A Guide to the Fairfax Harrison collection, 1730-1931
Library of Virginia
- Series V: Publications., Extent: 3 boxes. (Box 27-29)
  - American Turf Register--A Quarter Race in Kentucky, vol. 11, pp. 521-527. (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Some American Thoroughbred Breeders, a Calendar of the Studs Reported to the American Turf Register, 1830-1844. (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - American Turf Register, vol. 3, pp. 361, 423, 578-579. (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - American Turf Register, vol. 4, pp. 54-56, 381-383, 495-497, 548. (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - American Turf Register, vol. 5, pp. 329-330, 392, 444. (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - American Turf Register, vol. 6, pp. title, image, 1-2, 406-407, 428, 497-499. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - American Turf Register, vol. 7, pp. 67-69, 95, 225, 239, 363-365, 368, 456, 525-526, 571-576. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - American Turf Register--vol. 8, pp. 95-96, 256-258, 280-281, 285-288, 364, 406-409, 457-458, 495-499. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - American Turf Register--vol. 9, pp. 5-7, 12-13, 45-48, 142-144, 187-192, 239-240, 287-288, 297-300, 335-336, 383-384, 417, 575. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - American Turf Register--vol. 10, pp. 3-4, 25-30, 113-120, 355-357, 360-368, 427-429, 448-454, 483-484, 527-528, 532-536, 583-587. (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - American Turf Register--vol. 11, pp. 47-48, 97-100, 154, 194-200, 241-243, 252, 307, 324-326, 363-364, 366, 371-372, 426-428, 475-476, 491-492, 521-527, 556, 559-560, 655-656. (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - American Turf Register--vol. 12, pp. 165-166, 230-232, 342-344, 524-526, 590-592, 638-639, 691. (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - American Turf Register--vol. 13, pp. 107-108, 111-112, 284-288, 292, 350-352, 355-360, 408, 467, 471-472, 477-479, 529, 532, 536, 655, 699-700, 708. (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - American Turf Register--vol. 14, pp. 107-108, 134-135, 146-147, 157, 364, 367-371, 556, 622. (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - American Turf Register--vol. 15, pp. title, 128, 190, 639-640, 706. (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Spirit of the Times--vols. 8 and 9, excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Spirit of the Times--vol. 13, excerpts. (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Spirit of the Times, excerpts, 1843-1852. (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - English Stud Advertisements, 1743-1774. (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - First American Stud Book. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - American Stud Book--preface, 1837. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Stud Book, [1826]. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Two Early Private Stud Books. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - American Stud Book. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - The Background of the American Stud Book. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Stud book revisions. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - American Antiquarian Society, April 1915, pp. 130-192. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Animal Painters, Baily's Magazine, January 1897. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - The Cheney-Butler Prints, 1740-1753--index. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Collectanea for the Historian of the American Thoroughbred Horse from the Files of Skinner's American Farmer, etc. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Constitution, or Old Ironsides. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Dictionary of Artists (Graves). (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Early Maryland Pedigrees. (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Edgar's history of the Godolphin, 1827. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - the English Stallion in Ireland before 1760. (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - The Gentleman's New Pocket Farrier, 1830. (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - The Gentleman's New Pocket Companion, 1811. (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - The Horse of America. (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Imported English and Irish Horses. (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - My Life as a Slave by Charles Stewart, in Harper's New Monthly Magazine, October 1884. (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Observations on Livestock, 1804. (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Prints after James Roberts (Cheney-Butler prints). (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Pedigrees of Thoroughbred Horses. (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - The State of the Blood Horse in Virginia. (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Thomas Butler. (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - W. R. Johnson's Twenty-Mile Mare. (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Bibliography. (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Bibliography. (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Title pages. (Box 29, Folder 30)